# Jessica Graham

## Web Developer

#### **Jessica Graham**

D.O.B 27.06.1991

+44 7541017493

hellojessicagraham@gmail.com

#### **About Me**

I am a 25 year old New Zealander who has been living in England for 14 months. I have been learning JavaScript in my spare time for 8 months. Recently I have started to learn HTML and CSS.

I have built and published two websites using HTML and CSS which are both responsive and W3C compliant. Also I have experience using Git for version control, and host <u>various projects on Github</u>.

I am constantly continuing to develop my skills as a web developer, whether that be <u>experimenting with projects</u> on codepen, learning new tools like gulp and scss, or developing <u>websites</u>. Every day I am learning, and love what I do.

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/iamjessica">https://github.com/iamjessica</a>

Portfolio: www.hellojessica.co

Colourist Gallery: www.hellojessica.co/colourist

#### Education

#### **Team Treehouse**

- JavaScript Basics
- JavaScript Loops, Arrays and Objects
- HTML
- Introduction to HTML and CSS
- How to make a website

#### Codecademy

HTML & CSS

#### **Books**

- HTML and CSS
- JavaScript Programming

### **Employment History**

#### The Hair and Beauty Boutique / Colour Director

APRIL 2016 - OCTOBER 2016, SOLIHULL, ENGLAND

- Thoroughly consulting with clients and stylists to deliver colour services that meets clients needs.
- All chemical services and styling
- Educating clients. Prescribing in salon and at home care to ensure correct maintenance of service delivered
- Forming and retaining customer relationships
- Managing time effectively

#### Synergy Hair / Colour Director

AUGUST 2015 - OCTOBER 2015, WELLINGTON, NEW ZEALAND

- Thoroughly consulting with clients and stylists to deliver colour services that meets clients needs.
- All chemical services and styling
- Educating clients. Prescribing in salon and at home care to ensure correct maintenance of service delivered
- Forming and retaining customer relationships
- Managing time effectively
- Mentoring apprentices
- Training and presenting new collections to the team

#### Morgan and Morgan / Senior Colourist

DECEMBER 2014 - JULY 2015, AUCKLAND, NEW ZEALAND

- Thoroughly consulting with clients and stylists to deliver colour services that meets clients needs.
- Educating clients. Prescribing in salon and at home care to ensure correct maintenance of service delivered
- Forming and retaining customer relationships
- Managing time effectively

Referees

I am more than happy to supply referees if requested